<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>THNGS.</title><link>https://open-things.de/</link><description>Recent content on THNGS.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://open-things.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://open-things.de/aboutus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-things.de/aboutus/</guid><description>Hey, my name is Mirko Häberlin and I love to create Hardware with the intention to make it real products and not only plain PCB&amp;rsquo;s. I want to give them a purpose, a use-case and at the end as well a nice look. I have a training as technical assistant for medical devices and also a Bc.S in mediainformatics. In my last job I became hardware engineer where I combined both educations to create products from scratch.</description></item><item><title>AGB</title><link>https://open-things.de/agb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-things.de/agb/</guid><description>§1 Lorem Bacon ipsum dolor amet pig pork hamburger tenderloin burgdoggen spare ribs bacon pancetta pork loin tail turducken. Chicken pastrami jerky tongue ball tip strip steak. Ball tip alcatra turkey, cupim strip steak swine short loin tenderloin pancetta corned beef ribeye cow short ribs. Turkey turducken flank filet mignon beef ribs pastrami rump, andouille prosciutto picanha kevin strip steak. Corned beef fatback landjaeger hamburger alcatra, bacon buffalo tongue cow biltong salami sirloin swine.</description></item><item><title>Products</title><link>https://open-things.de/product/products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-things.de/product/products/</guid><description> Thread Sensor Tag Sensor for Pressure, Humidity, Temperature and Light
zum Shop</description></item><item><title>Thread Sensor Tag</title><link>https://open-things.de/product/thread_sensortag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-things.de/product/thread_sensortag/</guid><description>What is it? The Thread Sensor Tag is a low power sensor to measure pressure, temperature, humidity and light in a very small form factor running on a coin-cell battery for ~3 years. It uses OpenThread as a network and sends an MQTT* message every 20s with all informations incl. the battery status.
Features:
nRF52840 on a MS88SF2 module Light sensor VEMLS6030 @0x48 MS8607 with relative humidity @0x40, pressure and temperature @0x76 RGB LED Period Average Current deep sleep 3.</description></item></channel></rss>